<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>criterion</title>
    <link href="https://criterion.d8services.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://criterion.d8services.com" />
    <updated>2021-09-27T10:24:07+07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>ttyler</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://criterion.d8services.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Criterion App Privacy Policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>ttyler</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://criterion.d8services.com/criterion-app-privacy-policy.html"/>
        <id>https://criterion.d8services.com/criterion-app-privacy-policy.html</id>

        <updated>2021-09-27T09:56:51+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Flex App Privacy Policy Criterion by D8 Services Ltd. HK The Criterion App (from here on referred to as ‘The App’) was written by engineers from D8 Services Ltd., Hong Kong. The App will not work unless configured by a Jamf PRO Administrator to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Flex App Privacy Policy<br>Criterion by D8 Services Ltd. HK<br><br>The Criterion App (from here on referred to as ‘The App’) was written by engineers from D8 Services Ltd., Hong Kong. The App will not work unless configured by a Jamf PRO Administrator to access device data from an company owned Jamf PRO Server.<br><br>The App will access data directly with the credentials and serverURL as provided by the Jamf administrator through an App Configuration. There are no URLs accessed outside of this configuration, although the web page you offer must be standalone and have no links for this work.<br><br>D8 Services does not collect, store nor maintain ANY end user data aside from that provided by Apple in regards to the use, maintenance or communications via the Apple iOS App Store. We have zero interest in selling, storing, collecting nor manipulating end user data, further to this, D8 Services will never share data with any 3rd parties knowingly or maliciously. We want to make a product that can be deployed simply with no advertising and no ‘hidden’ costs, nor any in app purchases. As required by Apple policy, we do not share any personally identifiable data collected by our service with any third parties for any reason. The App has been released as a product for any organisation, business, university or school to use as they see fit.<br><br>No user data was harmed or will be harmed in the making of this policy.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to Criterion</title>
        <author>
            <name>ttyler</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://criterion.d8services.com/welcome-to-criterion.html"/>
        <id>https://criterion.d8services.com/welcome-to-criterion.html</id>

        <updated>2021-09-27T10:24:07+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Criterion is a D8 Services App designed for B2B business's running Jamf's Jamf PRO MDM service. The aim is to offer an app showing your preferred web page, and an agree option to accept the content. The page you offer should have no links outside&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Criterion is a D8 Services App designed for B2B business's running Jamf's Jamf PRO MDM service. The aim is to offer an app showing your preferred web page, and an agree option to accept the content.</p>
<p>The page you offer should have no links outside of the actual page, as the whole page is displayed to the end user.</p>
<p>Once you have contacted D8 Services for access to this App you will be granted access via the Apple Business Manager Apple School Manager Volume Purchasing program.</p>
<p>Once the app is visible in your Jamf PRO Server it must be configured, this is done via an App Config, see below.</p>
<p><code>&lt;dict&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;serverURL&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;$JPS_URL&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;apiCredentials&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;api Credentials Here&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;deviceID&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;$JSSID&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;pageTitle&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Agree and Submit&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;buttonText&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Submit&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;descriptionText&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Agree to terms and Conditions&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;URLToOpen&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;https://flex.d8services.com/flex-app-privacy-policy/&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;extensionAttribute&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;AgreeToThis&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;valueToSubmit&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Agreed&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;goodSubmissionText&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Submission was sucessfully posted to your server.&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;badSubmissionText&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;Submission to your server failed. Please try again&lt;/string&gt;<br> &lt;key&gt;ToggleSlider&lt;/key&gt;<br> &lt;string&gt;You must agree to this first&lt;/string&gt;<br>&lt;/dict&gt;</code></p>
<p>As such a simple app you may wonder why do we include so many options, quite simply it is for other countries to customised the text displayed to their users, we do after all have more than english as a language.</p>
<p>I have included a link <a href="https://criterion.d8services.com/criterion-app-privacy-policy.html">here</a> for you to see the Criterion privacy statement, there are zero links on this page, in order for the end user to be on one page, and not navigate away.</p>
<p>For the App Config, please fee free to change the "Strings" to match your site requirements, for API Credentials we have created a small app for our Flex app, which will enable you to <a href="https://github.com/D8Services/flexmdm/releases/tag/1.0" title="FlexEncoder for accessing an app to encrypt your credentials" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ofuscate your credentials</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
